A Finding Aid to the Henri Gallery Records, circa early 1900s, 1940-1996, bulk 1957-1995, in the Archives of American Art AAA.henrgall
Archives of American Art
- Alphabetical Files, 1947-1996; Series 2; 50.1 Linear feet Boxes 3-52, 55-57, OV 58
  - Name Files, 1947-1996; 2.1
    - Morgan, Thomas, circa 1957-1981 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Morin, Gerald, 1970-1973 (Box 33, Folder 29-30)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Mowder, John, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Mueller, Louis, 1987-1991 (Box 33, Folder 33-34)
    - Muller, Lisa, 1988-1994 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Mullins, Kevin, 1982-1994 (Box 33, Folder 36-38)
    - Multiples, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Murray, Clark, circa 1967; 1975 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Murray, Dan, 1990-1996 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, 1988-1994 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - The Museum of Modern Art (MOMA), 1962-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Museum of Modern Art (MOMA), Information, circa 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Naito, Rakuko, 1972-1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Nakashima, Tom, 1973-1995 (Box 34, Folder 8-15)
    - Namrol, Lloyd, circa 1967-1981 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Narbutovskih, Paula, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - National Collection of Fine Arts [Smithsonian Institution], 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - The National Portrait Gallery (Dr. Fern), 1990 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Navarro, Josep, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Neal, Reginald, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Neider, Alan, 1975-1992 (Box 34, Folder 24-27)
    - Nelson, David, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Nelson, Karen, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Nelson, Pam, 1987-1990 (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
    - Nesbitt, Lowell, 1964-1973 (Box 35, Folder 5-7)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1976-1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Nicholas Wilder Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Nichols, Ed, 1965-1972 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Nichols, Frederick, 1974-1977 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Nicholson, Peter, 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Nicoll, Robert, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Nierman, Leonardo, circa 1960s-1981 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Niewald, Wilbur, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Niewerth, Richard A., circa 1969 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Noe, Jerry, 1968-1980; 1991 (Box 35, Folder 17-19)
    - Noe, Jerry, [Disassembled Binder 1], 1974-circa 1976 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Noe, Jerry, [Disassembled Binder 2], 1974-circa 1977 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Noland, Kenneth, circa 1966-1970 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Norris, William, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Not New Consignment Shop, 1948-circa 1955 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Now Festival (April 1966, Washington, DC), 1964-1966; 1974 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Nowak, Jean, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Oberg, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Occidental Life Insurance, 1968-1982 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Ojile, Timothy, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Okigbu, Olaf, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Olitski, Jules, circa 1972 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Olsen, Eric, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 32-33)
    - Omwake, Bill, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Orzel, Rita, 1982-1995 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Osborne, John (Jon), circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Ossi, James, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Outerbridge, Graeme, 1977-1985 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Outerbridge, Graeme, 1975-1983 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - Owsley, Lowell, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Padovan, Mario, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Padwo, Saul, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Pagano, Alfonse, 1988-1994 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Pagano, Alfonse?, circa 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 1
    - Page, Lee, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Paine, James, 1969-1975 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Painter, Ernest, circa 1957-1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Parker, Beth, 1983-1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Parker, Margaret, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Parr, Mary, circa 1957-1981 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Pavlovic, Steve, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Pawlaczyk, Paul, 1987-1993 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Peabody, Bo, circa 1957-1981 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Pease, David, 1959 or 1964 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Peerless, Mitchell, circa 1972 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Peirce, Trevor, 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Peire, Luc, 1964-1980 (Box 36, Folder 21-26)
    - Peirick, David L., 1976-1990 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Pelino, Philip E., circa 1973 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Pereira, Rice, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Perlman, Joel, 1980-1989; 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Perlman, Mark, 1981-1987 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Perry, Beatrice, 1984-circa 1990 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Pershing, Louise, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Petersburg Press, Inc., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Pfeffer, Tanya, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Pickering, Cindia, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Pienich, David, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Pina, Scott T., 1991 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Pinsker, Essie, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Pištěk, Theodor, 1984-circa 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Polke, Sigmar, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Pollock, Charles, 1965-1989 (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
    - Pollock, Jackson, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pope, Mary Ann Irwin, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Poriotis, George, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Porter, Katherine, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Posey, Ernest, 1965-1979 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Prager, Eleanor K., circa 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Preissler, A., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Prendergast, 1965; 1967 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Priebe, Karl, 1960-1966; 1947 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Protech, Max, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Puig, José, 1970-1980 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
    - Puig, José, [Artwork], 1971 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Purins, Girts, 1978-1986 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
    - Purvis, Robert, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Puryear, Martin, circa 1971-1977; 1988; 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 22-23)
    - Quaytman, Harvey, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Quisgard, Liz, circa 1985-1988; 1966-1971 (Box 37, Folder 25-27)
    - Rabel, H. Marcel, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Rabkin, Leo, 1965, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Raimondi, John, circa 1960s-1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Ramsey, Ted, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1988; 1991 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Rayo, Omar, circa 1964 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Reder, Ronnie, circa 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Redman, Charles, Ambassador and Mrs., 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Reed, Paul, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Reiback, Earl Martin, circa 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Reich, Murray, 1971-1980 (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
    - Reif, David, 1979-1983 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Reinhardt, Ad, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Renouf, Edward, 1962-circa 1971 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Rettich, Jerome, 1966-1969 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 2
    - Ribalta, Pedro J., 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Rice, Anthony, 1969-1984 (Box 38, Folder 18-19)
    - Rice, Garry, 1971-1981 (Box 38, Folder 20-21)
    - Richards, Bill, 1972-1977 (Box 38, Folder 22-23)
    - Richardson, Bill, circa 1985 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Riches, Gregory, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - John and Mable Ringling Museum, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Riopelle, Jean-Paul, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Risley, John, circa 1965 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Robbins, Vincent, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Rockburne, Dorothea, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Rogers, Michael, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Roseberry, Bill, 1983-1987 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Rosenberg, Adrienne, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - [Rosenburg?], Mitchell, circa 1988 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1968; 1977 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Ross, Tom, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Rothko, Mark, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Rowe, Charles A., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Rudge, John, circa 1957-1981 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Ruhe, Ben, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Ruppert, John, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Russell, Laura, 1974-1985 (Box 38, Folder 42-43)
    - Russo, John, 1983-1991 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Ryan, William, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Rydingsvärd, Ursula von, 1980-1988 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - Saar, Betye, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Saba, Richard, 1980-1990 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Sachs, Samuel, circa 1957-1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Sadequain, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Saganic, Livio, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
    - Sander, Ludwig, 1967-1973; 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Sanford, Enid, 1991-1994; 1965-1977 (Box 39, Folder 11-13)
    - Sarayanon, Billy, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Sassano, Roseanne, 1975-1994 (Box 39, Folder 15-16)
    - [Sassano, Roseanne?], 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Savelli, Angelo, circa 1968-1981 (Box 39, Folder 18-21)
    - Scanga, Italo, 1971-1993 (Box 39, Folder 22-28)
    - Scanga, Italo, 1970-1990 (Box 40, Folder 1-9)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 3
    - Scanga, Italo, Biographies, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Scanga, Italo, California Collectors, 1970-1989 (Box 40, Folder 11-12)
    - Scanga, Italo, "Figures: Form and Fiction", 1988 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Scanga, Italo, Matthews Hamilton Gallery, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Scanga, Italo, Recent, 1982-1993 (Box 40, Folder 15-16)
    - Scanga, Italo, Resumes - Recent, circa mid-1980s-1989 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Scanga, Italo, Sales - Recent, 1970-1989 (Box 40, Folder 18-19)
    - Scarfe, Gerald, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Schaefer, Rita Leonard, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Schatz, Lincoln, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Schatz, Lincoln, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Schiele, Egon, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Schles, Ken, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Schlosser, Peter, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Schneemann, Carolee, 1978-1988 (Box 41, Folder 5-7)
    - Schneider, Jane [Diassembled Binder], 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Scholder, Fritz, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Schreuder, Jan, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Schwaib, Susan, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Schwake, circa 1957-1967 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 4
    - Schwartz, Kit, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Schwebler, Yuri, 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Schwedler, William, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Scott, David Settino, 1986-1993 (Box 41, Folder 16-20)
    - Scott, Tom, circa 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Sculpture Space, 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 22-23)
    - Seawright, Sandy, circa 1980s-1996 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Seltzer, Joanne L., circa 1978 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Senseny, Scott, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Serra, Richard, 1966-1972 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Sevy, Elen, circa 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Sexton, Barbara, 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Shack, Richard, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Shafer, Cary, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Shafer, Stan, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Shank, John, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Shannon, Joseph, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Shapiro, Babe, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Shapiro, David, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Shapiro, Irvin, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Shark's Incorporated, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Sharpe, David, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Shashaty, Yolanda, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Shaw, Reesey, 1975-1989 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Shaw, Toni, circa 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Shedletsky, Stuart, circa 1970 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Shelley, J.B., Jr., 1970; 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Shepley, Julia, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Shepp, Alan, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Shine, Aneta Georgievska, 1989-1995 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Shipley, Roger, 1969-1981 (Box 42, Folder 9-10)
    - Shiy, De Jinn, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Shulman, Arline, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Sihvonen, Oli, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Silver, Thomas, circa 1969-1980 (Box 42, Folder 14-15)
    - Silvester, James, 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Simonds, Charles, 1969-1988 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Simons, Vera, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Simpson, David, 1966-1969; 1981 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Simpson, Tommy, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Singer, Mike, 1969-1970; 1984 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Singley, George, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Slack, D.E., 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Slapion, Paul, 1986-1991 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Slavko, circa 1959 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Sloane, Phyllis, circa 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Slovart, circa 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Smelser, Larry, 1977-1991 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Breck, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Smith, Clemon E., 1979-1994; 1968 (Box 42, Folder 30-32)
    - Smith, Craig N., 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Smith, David, circa 1969; 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Smith, John Wallace, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Smith, James Walton, circa 1957-1981 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Lawson, 1973-1994 (Box 43, Folder 5-8)
    - Smith, Lawson, New, 1988-1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Lawson, Resumes, circa 1974-1988 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Richard, circa 1957-1981 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Smith-Fox, Patricia, circa 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian Associates, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Smukler, Barbara, 1973-1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Smyth, David, 1985; 1990; circa 1971-1974 (Box 43, Folder 15-17)
    - Snodgrass, James, 1962-1966 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Snyder, George, 1986-1990; 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 19-22)
    - Snyder, Joan, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Sockwell, Carroll, 1992; 1969 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Soffer, Sasson, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Sokolova, Marina, 1989-1993 (Box 43, Folder 26-28)
    - Sokolova, Marina, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Solomon, Jack, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Sonfist, Alan, 1971-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Sorgini, Antonio, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Soshanna, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby's [Warhol Book Consignment], 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Spofforth, John, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
    - Sporny, Stanley, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Stackhouse, Robert, 1972-1991 (Box 44, Folder 10-22)
    - Stackhouse, Robert [Disassembled Binder], 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Stackhouse, Robert and Mary Beth Edelson, 1970s-1980s (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Stern, Rudi (and Jackie Cassen), 1967 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Steward, Norm, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Stoller, Evan, 1979-1982 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Stoller, Evan, 1992; 1977-1982 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
    - Stone, Sylvia, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Stopher, Tom, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Storm King Art Center (Maps), circa 1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Streeter, Tal, circa 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Strider, Marjorie, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Strong, Piper, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Strunck, Juergen, 1970-1977 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
    - Stubbs, Al, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Studenroth, Jeffery E., 1977 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Sudnik, John, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Sugiyama, Minoru, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Sullivan, Bill, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Sullivan, James, circa 1971-1992 (Box 45, Folder 16-17)
    - Summers, Carol, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Sumrall, Jeff, 1989-1995 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Supplee, Sarah, 1968-1977 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Suyeoka, George, circa 1988-1991 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Swain, Robert, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Swetson, John, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Sylvester, Matt, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Syme, Robert, III, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Tacha, Athena, 1966-1980 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
    - Tadé, circa 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Tager, Harold, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Takahashi, Kiyoshi, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Takis, circa 1963 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Tanner, Henry Ossawa, 1971; 1991 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Tàpies, Antoni, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Taylor, Jan, 1988-1993 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Taylor, Thomas F., 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Tenney, Chica, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Tepper, Martha F., 1978 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Tessem, Susan, circa 1968-1974 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Thiebald, Wayne, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Thieler, Fred, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Thomas, Alma, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Thompson, Elliott, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Thompson, Richard, 1968-1990 (Box 45, Folder 43-47)
    - Thompson, Richard, Drawings, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 48)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 5
    - Thornton, Josephine, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Tilley, Jon and Lorna Swoboda, 1979-1982 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Tinguely, Jean, circa 1963-1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Tobey, Mark, circa 1971-1976 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Tobias, Julius, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Todd, Mike, 1962-1989 (Box 46, Folder 5-7)
    - Tomc, Tom, circa 1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Toral, Tabo, 1981-1994 (Box 46, Folder 9-13)
    - Toumayan, Eric, circa 1970s-1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Towbin, Irene K., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Trapp, Wayne, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Tressler, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Trotter, Serge, circa 1967-1981 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Tsai, circa 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Tsuhouhar, Foujita, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Twombly, Cy, 1990; 1994 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Umland, James, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Vallila, Marja, 1970-1994 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Van Alstine, John, 1978-1984 (Box 46, Folder 24-26)
    - Van Brunt, Philip, circa 1963-1986 (Box 46, Folder 27-30)
    - Van Brunt, Philip, 1966-1983 (Box 47, Folder 1-5)
    - Van Brunt, Philip, Recent, 1966-1987 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Van Buren, Curt, 1978-1985 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Van Dijk, James, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Van Germert-Lucy, Jeanne, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Van Gogh, Vincent, circa 1980s-1996 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Van Houten, Harold, 1983-1995 (Box 47, Folder 11-14)
    - Van Houten, Jeanne, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Van Roijen, Hildegarde, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Van Winkle, Lester, circa 1970-1993 (Box 47, Folder 17-18)
    - Vander Sluis, George, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Vasa, 1972-1989 (Box 47, Folder 20-22)
    - Vaughn, Reginald, circa 1993 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Vaux, Dick, 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Victoria, Ted, 1968-1977 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Victoria, Ted, 1991; 1987; 1968-1977; Includes 1 sound cylinder: 45 rpm (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
    - Vinograd, Martha, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Vitale, Magda, 1988-1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Vogl, Don, 1978-1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Wade, Robert, circa 1971-1974 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Wagner, Gale, 1972-1977; 1988 (Box 48, Folder 8-10)
    - Walburg, Gerald, 1969-1973; 1988-circa 1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Waldinger, Janna, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Waldman, Paul, circa 1960s (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Walker, Bilhenry, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Walker, Ed, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Walker, John, 1972-1975 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Walker, Longhorne, circa 1970s (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Wall, Brian, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Wallin, Lawrence, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Walton, Shigeko Sato, 1972-1980 (Box 48, Folder 20-21)
    - Walz, Randy G., 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Ward, Tricia, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1993-1995 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Wasserman, David, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Watson, Genna, 1978-1983 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Weaver, Robert, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Weyhe, Arthur, 1972-1988 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Weignad, Charmion von, circa 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Weintraub, Linda, 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Weik, Roger, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Weisburd, Harry, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Wells, Lynton, circa 1974 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Wesselman, Tom, 1965-circa 1975 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - West, Troy, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Westbrook, Adell, 1982-1990; 1974 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Westermann, H.C., 1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, circa 1971 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Wheelock, George F., 1970-1973 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Where Washington, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Whistler, James McNeill, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - White, Robert, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - White, Saul, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Whitney, Mac, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, Tom Armstrong, 1971-1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Whitting, Peter, 1983-1995 (Box 49, Folder 10-15)
    - Wicht, John von, 1962-1964 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Wiles, Robert, 1973-1980; 1988 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Wiley, William T., 1972; 1970 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Willers, William, 1982-1994 (Box 49, Folder 19-20)
    - Williams, Bob, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Williams, Richard L., 1979 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Williams, Tom, 1984-1988 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Willis, Jay, 1971-1980 (Box 49, Folder 24-28)
    - Willis, Thornton, 1982-1996; circa 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 29-31)
    - Wilson, Ann, circa 1957-1996 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, May, 1957-1976 (Box 50, Folder 2-6)
    - Wolf, Nancy, 1971-1977 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Wolf, Nancy, Dead File, 1971-1979 (Box 50, Folder 8-10)
    - Wonderlick, Al, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Workshop, Inc., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Workshop Inc., Bills - All Paid, 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Woyt, Bruce, circa 1980s-1996 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Wright, Faith-dorian, 1984-1995 (Box 50, Folder 15-18)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Wright, MacDonald, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Wright, Rosemary, circa 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      Oversized material housed in Box 57, Folder 6
    - Wyatt, Lyn, circa 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Xavier, Hector, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Yamashita, Noboru, 1963-1967 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Yi, Jason, 1986-1995 (Box 50, Folder 25-27)
    - Yokoi, Rita, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Yoshida, Minoru, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Young, Peter, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Yust, David, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Zaborowski, Dennis John, circa 1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Zakanych, Robert, 1965-1973 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
    - Zakas, Katerina, circa 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Zambelis, John, 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Zapkus, Kes, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - [Zara], 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Zelenak, Edward, 1969-1978 (Box 51, Folder 12-13)
    - Zelt, Martha, 1976-1978 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Zeran, Kenneth, 1974-1990 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Zhurkov, Igor, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Zimmerman, Catherine, circa 1967-1971 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Zimmerman, Jerome H., 1979 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Zoline, Pamela, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Zucker, Joe, circa 1970s-1981 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Zuehlke, Dale, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 21-22)
    - Unidentified, Film Reel, 1963 August 3; 1 film reel: 8mm (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Various Artists, Years Ago Represent, 1978-1992 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Various Names, To Be Filed, circa 1984-1995; circa 1960s (Box 51, Folder 25-27)
    - Various Names, Unsorted, 1983-1995; 1972 (Box 51, Folder 28-30)
    - Various Names, Unsorted, 1983-1995; 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
    - Restricted Folders, 1974-1990 (Box 55, Folder 2-11)